(Stuart:)Yeah, I don't recall any offers.
But, you know, uh, I-I'm glad
it worked out the way it did
(Stuart:)because I got to know
this wonderful person.
(Howard(on phone):)Yeah.
(Raj:)Mrs. Wolowitz was
pretty special.
(Raj:)When I first moved to America,
(Raj:)Howard was my only friend.
(Raj:)She made me feel
so welcome in her home.
(Raj:)Which says a lot,
because, those first few years,
(Raj:)she thought I was the gardener.
(Penny:)Whenever I saw her,
(Penny:)she'd say I was too skinny
and try and feed me.
(chuckles)
(Amy:)She did that to me, too.
(Penny:)Don't take this away from me.
(Sheldon:)I didn't care
for her yelling.
(Sheldon:)But now that I'm not going
to hear it again,
(Sheldon:)I'm sad.
(Nathan Fillion:)If you want,
I can yell at you later.
(Sheldon:)It won't be as good.
(Leonard:)Let's have a toast.
(Leonard:)To Mrs. Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)A loving mother...
(Leonard:)...to all of us.
(Leonard:)We'll miss you.